&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：下面是一个尝试
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's an example that tries to
指出这不是快照。
point out that it's not a snapshot.
而这似乎是开发人员经常遇到的挫折感之一。
And this is one of the perpetual frustrations that developers seem to have.
他们得到了这个想法，好的结束，但是他们立即跳了起来
They get this idea, okay closure, but then they immediately jump
这意味着我正在拍摄一个值的快照。
to the assumption that that means that I'm snapshoting a value.
我在某个时刻捕捉到了一些价值。
That I'm capturing some value at some moment.
这不是结束的意思。
That is not what closure is.
事实上，闭包与值根本没有任何关系。
Closure has not got anything to do with the values at all, as a matter of fact.
你不会因为一个值而关闭。
You don't close over a value.
我在博客和书籍中见过无数次。
I've seen that countless times in blogs and books.
没有这样的事情，那是胡说八道，
There is no such thing, that is nonsense,
没有关闭价值这回事。
there's no such thing as closing over a value.
您关闭了一个变量，这意味着您有一个到该变量的链接。
You close over a variable, which means you have a linkage to that variable.
这意味着在你访问它的时候，
Which means at the time you access it,
你看到的是那个变量在那个时刻的值，而不是它以前的值。
you're seeing whatever value that variable has at that moment, not it had before.
在本例中，当我在第3行上创建myTeacher函数时，
Here in this example when I create the myTeacher function on line 3,
那一刻老师就有了凯尔的价值。
at that moment teacher has the value Kyle.
然后后来我把老师换成了价值苏西。
And then later I change teacher to the value Suzy.
然后是第9行，当我执行函数时，它将打印什么？
And then line 9 when I execute the function what's it gonna print?
不是Kyle，我们没有关闭Kyle的值，我们关闭了变量教师。
Not Kyle, we didn't close over the value Kyle, we closed over the variable teacher.
当我们执行该函数时，我们将访问它的值。
And when we execute that function, we're gonna access the value of it.
它是一个指向您关闭的所有变量的实时链接。
It is a live link to all the variables that you are closed over.
所以不要把闭包看作是获取价值，
So don't think of closure as capturing values,
可以把它看作是保留对变量的访问。
think of it as preserving access to variables.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这个咬人最多，最经典的地方
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The place where this bites people the most, the most classic
规范示例是，每当您尝试在for循环内创建闭包时，或者
canonical example, is whenever you try to create closures inside of a for loop, or
任何一种循环机制的内部。
inside of any kind of looping mechanism.
通常不使用计时器，但这只是一个方便的例子。
Not usually with timers, but that's just a convenient illustration here.
通常情况下，这就像将单击处理程序分配给按钮数组
Normally it's like assigning click handlers to an array of buttons for
例如。
example.
这个函数，在每次迭代中创建，它的外观如下
And this function, that is being created in each iteration, it has the appearance
它所做的是在每次迭代中关闭I值。
that what it's doing is closing over the i value in each iteration.
所以我们期待它打印出I 1，I 2，I 3，但是
So we're expecting it to print out i 1, i 2, i 3, but
当我们运行时，它会打印出4，4，4。
when we run it it prints out 4, 4, 4.
为什么？
Why?
因为只有一个i变量。
Cuz there's only one i variable.
第一行有一个i变量，并且只有一个变量，并且
There's an i variable on line 1 and there's only one of them, and
我们有三个功能。
we have three functions.
如果我们想要有三个单独的值，我们需要多少个变量？
If we wanted to have three separate values, how many variables would we need?
这不是难数学。
This is not hard math.
如果我们想要三个单独的值，我们需要多少个变量？
If we wanted three separate values, how many variables do we need?
我们需要三个变量，对吧？
We need three variables, right?
而且只有一个，所以它当然只能有一个值。
And there's only one, so of course it can only have the one value.
在这种情况下，它将具有发生的值
And in this case, it's gonna have the value that occurs
在循环的末尾，即值4。
at the end of the loop, which is the value 4.
我们不能有效地使用封闭性，除非我们将自己与之分开
We can't effectively use closure until we separate ourselves from that
捕获价值的感知。
perception of capturing values.
它不是捕获一个值，保留对变量的访问，好吗？
It's not capturing a value, preserving access to a variable, okay?
所以，如果我们想解决这个问题，而且
So, if we wanted to solve this problem, and
我们分析了，我需要单独的变量，我们已经看到
we analyzed that, I need separate variables, we've seen
如何创建变量的几个不同示例。
several multiple different examples of how to create variables.
如果我们想创建多个同名变量，
If we wanna create more than one variable with the same name,
我们需要做新的范围，对吧？
we need to make new scopes, right?
所以我们可以在这里做一个不确定的，但是现在我们有了ES 6更常见的方法，
So we could do an iffy here, but the much more common way now that we have ES six,
现在我们有了块显微镜，
now that we have blockscoping,
只是在迭代中粘贴一个块范围的声明。
is to just stick a block scoped declaration in the iteration.
现在让j在每次4循环迭代时运行。
So now let j is going to run every time the 4 loop iterates.
它将在循环的整个新迭代中创建一个全新的j。
And it's gonna create a whole new j in that whole new iteration of the loop.
当我们在第4行关闭它时，我们将关闭一个全新的j。
When we close over it on line 4, we are closing over a whole new j.
有三个独立的js，因此我们得到它们中的值1，2和3。
There are three separate js and therefore we get the values in them 1, 2, and 3.
看到捕获值和关闭变量之间的区别了吗？
See the difference between capturing a value and closing over a variable?
事实证明，有一个甚至，我认为更好的一些人可能会说更狡猾，但
It turns out there's an even, I think better some people might say trickier, but
有一个更好的方法来解决这个问题。
there's an even better way of solving this problem.
因为我一直在为var i和
Because that perpetual problem of I'm doing for var i and
我的闭包没有捕捉到价值。
my closures aren't capturing the value.
这对于JavaScript开发人员来说已经有20年的时间了。
That's been a problem for JavaScript developers for like 20 years.
他们决定用iOS6，好吧，为什么我们不直接去
They decided with iOS six, well, why don't we just go ahead and
这样，如果你在你的
make it so that if you use a let on your for
循环我们将自动为每个迭代创建一个新的i。
loop we'll automatically create a new i for each iteration.
而不是仅仅创建一个属于整个
Instead of creating just one that belongs to the whole for
循环这里，每一次迭代都会有一个全新的i。
loop here there's gonna be a brand new i for each iteration.
这意味着闭合就会神奇地起作用，好吗？
Which means the closure just magically works, okay?
关键是如果您需要对您关闭多个不同的值
The point is if you need multiple different values being closed over you
需要多个不同的变量。
need multiple different variables.
您需要关闭不同的变量，而不是试图捕获值。
You need to close over different variables, not try to capture values.
凯尔·辛普森：什么事？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以，I实际上是在里面定义的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So, the i is defined actually inside,
尽管它是这样写的，但是它实际上是在块中定义的吗？
even though it's written this way, but is it actually then defined inside the block?
基本上是这样吗？
Is that basically what it is?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，它被解释为好像每个迭代都有一个新的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, it is interpreted as if each iteration there's a new
声明，JavaScript负责为其赋值
declaration of i, and JavaScript takes care of assigning it the value that it
如果它的表亲在前一次迭代结束时有。
had that its cousin had at the end of the previous iteration.
它会帮你把所有的东西都连接起来。
It wires up all that stuff for you.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：是否还有其他情况也适用或
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is there any other case were that applies as well or
只有这个吗？
is that the only one?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所有For循环形式都有For let方差。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All of the for loop forms have a for let variance.
所以在这里，我们必须让大家知道。
So for here, we have for let of.
我们已经让，&gt；&gt；扬声器4：每个？
We have let, &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Each?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嗯，每个都不是句法形式。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well, for each isn't a syntactic form.
这是一个迭代器，所以你已经得到了一个函数。
That's a iterator, so you already get a function with that one.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：[咳嗽]但是是的，for，for of，for in，这三个句法
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: [COUGH] But yeah, for, for of, and for in, those three syntactic
for循环自动在迭代中创建它们的东西。
for loops automatically make their thing inside of the iteration.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：顺便说一下，就像一个小细节，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: By the way, just as a little tiny detail,
不是很多人会遇到这个。
not that many people are gonna run across this.
但如果你真的尝试使用常量，
But if you did try to use a const there,
你会得到一个错误，因为I+正在试图修改变量。
you're gonna get an error because that i++ is trying to modify the variable.
所以在这里你需要使用一个let。
So here you would need to use a let.
所以闭合是一种联系的保存
So closure is a preservation of the linkage
变量，而不是值的捕获。
to a variable, not the capturing of the value.